you stop?
I don't know it SHUT IT
I'm not gonna give my heart I'm
not gonna give my friends Let's
see how strong your strength
is I'm not gonna give it to you
But if there's any way that you
have to You can still do it You
can still do it That's my
best way to let me know I'm not
gonna give it a game I'll show
you the chance I can Let's do it.
Ah!
It's Straw Hat and Jinbei! They're strong!
Crazy strong! Watch out!
The hell am I, chopped liver?
Hurry, okay?
I am hurrying!
I want to get up there and
kick Kaido's ass already!
Little shit!
Come here!
You guys really aren't worth a damn.
I'm sorry, General Fourtricks.
General Hamlet, we gave it our
best, but it wasn't enough.
A word comes to mind when I think
of you, and that word is common.
As for us, exceptional, of course.
Beyond expectations.
The strong keep their mouths shut, Hamlet.
They let their actions speak for them.
General Fourtricks!
That looks wrong!
General Pantlet, no!
Kai, no!
I'm coming for you!
Get
off
the
rooftop immediately! Yes, sir!
You may begin. I'm ready.
We must continue. Can you stand?
Of course I can.
That's just what I'd expect of you.
Your courage never seems to run out.
You know, you samurai impress me.
Just like Roger and Whitebeard.
They knew what it meant to be gold.
both their stories had proper endings
perhaps it's old-fashioned
but I believe death
completes a man I'm sure
you must feel the same
so why don't we finish this
don't be so arrogant you monster
do you think getting killed
by you would be an honor
Never!
So how are you digging
my playgrounds, boys?
Not like this!
It's cold!
Somebody...
It's me, your buddy!
Wouldn't you rather bite a samurai?
Mr.
Queen, why are you doing this to us?
My body! Oh, no!
It's all over me!
Get him off me!
Your pleasures are all failures,
and all you can do is laugh!
Now you can be useful just this once!
Somebody help!
Poor man asked you for help
and you just cut him down?
That was the only way I could help him.
He was becoming an Oni.
I suppose you're right.
Well, that aside, has
anyone seen the captain?
He'll be fine.
Wherever he is, I bet we've got it worse.
No mercy even for their allies?
Dammit!
I'm sorry.
I got sloppy back there, boss.
Now I must do the art of the
thing and protect my friend!
Don't be hasty, you damn fool!
I don't want to be around here!
We can find a cure, I know it!
If there's nothing left for us to try,
then and only then shall I finish you.
Don't sacrifice yourself!
You're losing ground.
There has to be something we can do.
Tell us, Chopper.
I can't fight and make medicine.
Also, we'll have to administer shots
to all the Oni and that won't be easy.
So, uh...
This is tough, but we do
have one thing on our side.
Unlike in Udon, the virus creator's here.
There's no way he would design something
so deadly and not make an antibody.
He must have it somewhere.
It's the best chance we've got right now.
If we get that, I can make medicine easy.
I don't think that easy is the word.
We'll have to take the
cure from a lead performer.
With medicine, I should be able
to make the symptoms go away,
but they might be in bad shape after that.
They gained incredible
strength when they transformed,
but their skin was exposed to
extreme cold—that's too much strain.
I'm afraid their bodies can't handle it.
These
guys get back up in no time,
almost like they're zombies—no,
if we aren't able to get that
cure, those people will die.
Once you get infected,
you'll have an hour to
live if you're lucky.
you're lucky
That can't be those ice honey down
there are good friends, right?
Right now, they're giving
it all they've got.
This is a big moment for
them Then
you'll be next.
You damn sicko!
How many of these freaky viruses?
You gotta make before you're happy!
Screw this floor!
I'm outta here.
Hey.
Open the damn door!
It's brother Apu.
Huh.
What is this stuff?
That is the only vial of
antibody for the virus.
Uh, and he gave it to me?
Lose it and I'll kill you!
You dig.
Uh, what?
An antibody?
And he has it?
There's an antibody?
Then there's hope.
Queen presents Game Time!
It is!
Let's party, hearty buddy,
cause it's time to play.
You wanna win the game
to make that sucker pay.
Murder, betrayal, I ain't gonna lie.
Cause in an hour, sucker,
you are gonna die.
It's pandemonium.
How could you?
These are people's lives you're
playing with Ice only tag.
You better hurry, boy!
Son of a...
Come on!
Zoro!
Get that file and bring
it back to me! Got it!
Don't let them have it!
Or people will die!
Don't let the samurai get the cure!
Queen, come on, buddy!
This is too much even for you!
Time starts now!
Better hurry!
Run or die!
If they don't catch you,
then you win, brother!
But everyone else will take the bucket!
Damn it, Queen!
You seriously want to
fight for the Kozuki?
Or maybe you'd rather carry
them on your back and run away.
Well, whatever.
We don't have to beat you.
Our only mission is to kill the Void.
Don't listen to him.
I'll keep you safe, I swear.
You're risking your life?
For me?
For the Kozuki?
Whoever you are, it doesn't
matter now if you'll help us.
Please save our young lord!
I beg you!
I'll save him, Shinobu.
You as well. What?
Twenty years ago, I saw
Kozuki Oden's execution.
You live in peace and
none of you know why.
Who the hell do you think ensured that?
The entire time, Lord Odin
has been protecting Wano.
So why don't you tell me again?
Who are you calling a fool?
The speech you gave that
day brought me to tears.
More than that, Kozuki Oden's
way of life has inspired me!
Momonosuke, on that terrible
day, I had hoped to save you,
so I ran to Kuri.
Wait, you're okay?
But in the end,
all I could do was watch powerless as
Kaido held you over the edge of the castle.
I'm sorry I failed you.
I was weak, but not now, not anymore!
Huh?
Who are you, really? Tell me!
Who said that you were my father?
Kozuki Udon!
But…
I have another name.
Yamato!
And I shall lay down my life for you!
Damn you, Marco!
I don't know my role in this story
yet, but I do know your bad news!
You're the last thing Straw Hat and
his allies need to deal with right now!
Ha!
Hey!
Come here, Prometheus!
Yes, Mama.
You ready?
Heavenly fire!
Ships are sailing to a new era, but
there's no room on them for you!
Oh, shut up!
Why is his flame stronger than mine?
Rometheus, no!
Phoenix Fire's a rare breed.
Don't know what to tell you, bro.
You think you're cute, huh?
I'll show you!
Ma-ma-ma-ma!
I've got you now, bird brain.
Should've minded your own business.
Now, pettispatto, shoot him down!
Mama, look.
I do apologize to you, Marco.
Our Lickety Alliance was short-lived.
Well, this sucks.
I once longed to kill you,
but now it's just a formality.
Oh, how ironic.
Ha-ha!
Daddy!
Wade!
You!
You're the one who attacked us last time!
So you're here to thwart
me again, are you?
Is this the man?
Pedro's killer?
It's all his fault.
He deserves to suffer.
Don't blame me.
That idiot blew himself up.
It's like he's harassing
me from the damn afterlife.
This is my task.
This is the road that Pedro
set out for me and my friends.
Hugh Karoo.
We must keep moving forward!
What a pain in the ass.
I don't need to deal with
your petty revenge right now.
Couldn't they do it on their own time?
We are trying to fight a war here.
Have it your way!
Sorry, who are you?
My name is Carrot. That's Wanda.
And you, Tia, are Marco.
A friend of Master Cat
Viper, from what I've heard.
I suppose you could say that.
Bye-bye, Bernie.
If you still want to kill me,
come back some other time.
I can't afford to waste
any of my soul to beat you.
Follow her, Marco.
Leave him to us.
Kay, I'm counting on you, too.
Ah!
What in the hell is this?
Apu!
Give me that vial!
Leave me alone already!
Stop! Stop! No!
Come against one ain't fair, you cheaters!
Dammit!
Why don't you give up so
I can help Keenemon fight?
Drake, this loser's wasting my time.
Let's finish this.
That's fine with me.
I've always hated him.
I don't care!
I hate you too!
That's a real dick move, Drake.
Spying wasn't enough, so you
gotta be a straight-up traitor.
I see.
That's Roro Noa Zoro.
The Straw Hats have a couple
of big shots in the crew.
We had better take them down
before they cause any more trouble.
Wade, that's Judge's son.
He's with Straw Hat?
His family is the face
of Jeremiah Double Six.
And one of them is here?
Interesting.
As it turns out, I'm fine.
I mean, look at me.
No horns, nothing.
What a relief.
Your body temperature can't go
down because you're all bones.
You're cold as a corpse already.
I see.
That makes sense. Yes.
Why, I don't have any flesh or
organs for that matter, do I?
Even a fatal illness is
no threat to a corpse.
Wow, that is depressing.
But I'm invincible.
Wait a sec.
Brooke is a skeleton, so his temperature
didn't change when he was infected.
Also, the ice didn't spread.
That means the virus must be
spreading through the ice.
It's multiplying.
It happens because their body gets cold.
So then, we have to
maintain their temperature.
All right, but how is it freezing
their body from the inside?
Maybe I was wrong about how it works.
Chopper, your arm! What's happening?
How did I not notice?
Oh, no!
How did they get me?
All is lost!
Chopper's gonna die!
Special attack, Green Star!
Shibble!
Ew, ew, gross!
Gotcha!
Hell yeah!
If you can't beat them, dissolve them
with digestive fluid, I always say!
This stuff is nasty and
sticky, and I hate it!
Help me, baby!
Oh, baby!
You could have freed yourself, you whiner.
No fear!
Oh, baby, you're my hero!
Get off of me, you're
covered in slime, you maniac!
No fear!
Let's try this one!
Bambu-chamalain!
That attack was so basic.
No more games.
Because I am done playing around!
Ultimortar!
Not again.
Hold on, Usopp.
You're next, tramp.
Don't kill me.
I can't fight back. It's over.
You beat me. You won this.
You totally defeated me.
You think I don't know that already?
You've wasted enough of my time.
Now say it. Okay.
What do I say?
I told you loud and clear, didn't I?
Your captain pissed me off,
bragging about how he's going to beat
Commander Kaido and be King of the Pirates.
I'm sorry, you're right.
Luffy's an idiot.
And he talks too much.
Just don't headbutt me, I'm begging you.
I'll do anything.
I'll leave the island.
If you hit me again, I'm done.
I'll die.
I'll give you one last chance.
Say it loud and clear.
Say that your captain will
never be King of the Pirates!
Fine.
Luffy will...
He'll never...
Never be able to...
That's it, Nami.
It's okay to lie.
The truth isn't worth dying for.
Not after we've come this far.
Just lie to her, whatever it takes.
Luffy will...
Luffy will never...
never give up.
Till he wins.
So I'm sorry, he'll beat Kaido,
and he'll become King of the Pirates!
You had your chance.
Now die.
Get away, Nami, you dope! Hurry!
Oh, Nami!
Go!
Coming to ya!
The dog!
What is that?
It's Otama!
What are you doing here?